ROBERT HUMENANSKY

1352 Appaloosa Ave Kaysville, Utah 84037 (801) 513-5966 Home / (801) 599-2393 Cell

CAREER SUMMARY

Twenty years of Voice Engineering experience in the telecommunications industry with focus on Cisco's Unified Contact Center Enterprise (UCCE) solution. I have broad knowledge and expertise in virtualization, client-server networks, equipment, and processes used in the call center environment.

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

Certifications:	Training:
CCNP Collaboration – Cisco Certified Network	Amazon Web Services Essential Training
Professional - Nov 2016	
CCNP Voice – Cisco Certified Network	Programming Foundations: Web Services
Professional – Voice June 2013	
UCCEI – Unified Contact Center Enterprise	Cisco CVP
Implementation (642-242) May 2013	Installation and Maintenance
UCCES - Unified Contact Center Enterprise	Cisco Unified Web and eMail
Support (642-243) May 2013	Interaction Manager Enterprise (CEIM)
	Cisco UCCE
	Product Training and System Administration

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Optanix 2011 to Present

Kaysville, Utah

High Touch Team - UCC Engineer

- Create wiki docs to address requested monitoring enhancements
- Deploy latest Cisco Contact Center technologies in a virtualized environment.
- Automate device configuration and access testing using scripts (bash, Perl, Python)
- Research / Document various methods of Serviceability including SNMP polling, traps and REST API Calls
- Design and engineer a Contact Center Serviceability dashboard
- Familiar with Linux and MySQL which is used daily on the CaseSentry appliance

Day 2 Contact Center Engineer

2009 to 2011

- Provide Tier 2 TAC support for various Cisco products including ICM(UCCE), UCCX/IPIVR, CVP, CTI, CAD, CUIC, Finesse, and Call Manager.
- Monitor, update, and assist our customers via manual and auto trouble tickets using Case Sentry monitoring tool which remotely monitors customer's contact center environment.
- Perform log analysis, integrity checks, and make recommendations to customers on ways to optimize their contact center environment.

Robert Humenansky

Page Two

- Provide various levels of support via ESR (MAC) requests. These changes can consist of server maintenance for bare metal or UCS chassis, scripting logic changes for UCCE and UCCX platforms, and informational requests requiring research outside of normal break/fix support.
- Member of Cisco RMS (Remote Monitoring Services) team which maintains Day 2 customer relations and support for several large direct Cisco customers.

eLovalty 2006 to 2009

Austin, Texas

Senior Consultant

- Responsible for On-Boarding new clients for Day 2 support: (knowledge transfer from Project Team)
- Provide 2nd Level support for IPCC customers running either IPIVR or CVP
- Provide 2nd Level support for CTISVR, CTIOS, and CAD
- Install and maintain all components of IPCC including routers, loggers, PG's, AW's, etc
- Troubleshoot ICM scripts for call flow errors
- Use SQL Query Analyzer to assist in troubleshooting

RJH Technologies 2002 to 2006

Kaysville, Utah

Consultant

• Consult for various financial organizations with emphasis on network and data management

Providian Financial 1998 to 2002

Salt Lake City, Utah

Voice Engineer (1999-2002)

- Saved \$1.6M annually and simplified the operating environment through the conception and design of a VRU Farm utilizing TnT
- Reduced International-dialing costs by 30% with the implementation of VOIP to Argentina
- Converted IP network from public to private IP addresses. Paved the way for ATM network migration.
- Trained and mentored other engineers.
- Upgraded GeoTel/ICM system from 4.1 to 4.5 to 4.6.2 to take advantage of new technology interfaces.

Site Manager (1998-1999)

• Translated upper-management needs into a functional work plan.

EDUCATION

Keller Graduate School of Management, Online Study, 2001-2002 Obtaining MTM, (Masters in Telecommunications Management)

BS, (Bachelors of Science), Electronics Engineering Technology GPA 3.6 DeVry Institute of Technology, Columbus, Ohio 1989